Resume 2/3/21, 8:22 AM

PATRICIA ATTAH DATA SCIENTIST

Summary

Current graduate student in data scientist with a major in machine learning a statistical background including understanding of hypothesis testing, confidence intervals PCA, LDA and time series and experience with python, R, SAS and SQL. Applied knowledge of data processing, data mining and machine learning algorithms to solve practical business problems and find data driven solutions to increase efficiency. Some machine learning methods I have applied include classification, clustering, regression and neural networks.

Employment

Springboard Online Student May 2020 to Jan. 2021

Springboard Data Science Career Track - Student

Description: 550+ hours of hands-on course material, with 1:1 industry expert mentor, oversight, and completion of 2 in-depth capstone projects. Mastered skills in Python, SQL, data analysis, data visualization, hypothesis testing, and machine learning.

Jacobs Engineering

Structural Designer

Dallas Texas Feb. 2019 to Current

Design of structural building framework, substructure and superstructure. Elements include foundation, framework and roof. I used critical thinking to ensure adequate design. Applied problem solving skills where necessary. Developed deep understanding of software to produce adequate results and paid attention to detail to complete tasks on time and within budget.

Projects

Correlation between heart disease and certain biomedical traits

Aug. 2020 to Sept. 2020

machine learning classification model that uses several different algorithms tons which best predicts the outcome of heartsease.

Housing Price Prediction

June 2020 to July 2020

using regression to create a predictive model for house price prediction.

Life Expectancy Predictive model

Sept. 2020 to Oct. 2020

Creation of predictive model for the life expectancy with regression using various socioeconomic factors.

Records database design

Oct. 2020 to Oct. 2020

Relational database design using SQL

Stock Prediction ARIMA Vs LSTM

Oct. 2020 to Dec. 2020

Comparison of neural network to machine learning algorithms for prediction of stock using the LSTM and ARIMA models.

Contact

• https://github.com/trishattah/SB-DataScience-Track

**** 2147808010

Education

SMU May 2020 to Current
Masters Data Science 2021

Spring Jan. 2020 to Dec. board 2020

Certificate Data science 2020

University of May 2016 to Texas Arlington Dec. 2018
Masters Civil Engineering 2018

Skills

Machine Learning
Data Visualisation
Big Data
Data Mining
Problem solving
Python
SAS
R

https://resume.creddle.io/